A Guide to the L. T. Christian Funeral Home Records, 1912-1986
Library of Virginia
- Carrick, William Charles, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Carrington, Alexander McNeill, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Carrington, Carter Ingram, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Carrington, Delia D., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Carrington, Fred W. (2 folders), 1941 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Carrington, George, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Carrington, Hazel Dimmick, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Carrington, Tazewell M., Jr., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Carroll, John Otis, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Carroll, Judson Clifford, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Carroll, Leila Morris, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Carson, Marie Gresham, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Carson, Walter Lapsley, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Carter, [infant], 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Carter, Afton Barnes, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Carter, Agnes Mayo, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Carter, Alice Blair, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Carter, Anna Belle, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Carter, Anna Monk, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Carter, Bernard, 1942 (disinterred 1948) (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Carter, Bernard P., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Carter, Berta Atkinson, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Carter, Bettie S., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Carter, Blanche Augusta, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Carter, Blanche Frostick, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Carter, Blanche Jennings, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Carter, Carroll Windsor, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Carter, Chasteen, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Carter, Dave, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Carter, David Walker, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Carter, Ellen Ball [infant], 1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Carter, Ellen Virginia, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Carter, Emily Randolph Harrison, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Carter, Evie Blankenship, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Carter, Fernande Nenette Villeneuve, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Carter, Florence Henry Cosby, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Carter, H. C., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Carter, James Frank, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Carter, John William, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Carter, Lucile A., 1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Carter, Mary Surles, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Carter, Maurice Francis, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Carter, Nancy [infant], 1949 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Carter, Nannie French, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Carter, Norma Bell, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Carter, Percy G., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Carter, Robert James, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Carter, Robert Winston, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Carter, Spencer L., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Carter, Suzanne Villeneuve, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Carter, William Edward, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Carter, William Joseph, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Cary, Agnes R. B., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Cary, Agnes Ruffin, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Cary, Betty Willis, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Cary, John Reid, Jr., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Cary, Lottie Henderson, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Cary, Miles, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Cary, Stuart Bradley, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Casey, Nancy Carrington Anderson, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Caskie, Ambler, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Caskie, Emma Palmer, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Caskie, Gussie Millhiser, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Caskie, John Marshall, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Cason, James Irving, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Cason, Rosamond, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Cassell, Ellen T., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Cassell, Harry M., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Catlett, Marion Buckey, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Catlett, Richard Henry, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Catlin, Benjamin R., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Catlin, Ralph Horne, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Cauthorne, Emily Valiant, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Cauthorne, Ross Adolphus, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Cauthorne, Thomas Gordon, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Cave, Norma, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Cazentre, Virginia F., 1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Cecil, Ada Webb, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Cecil, Amanda Alston Drake, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cecil, Elva Early, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Cecil, Homer C., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Cecil, Luelva G., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Chaffin, Adaline Wilson, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Chaffin, Bertha Jones, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Chaffin, James Lewis, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Chaffin, Lucille Virginia, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Chaffin, Richard Booker, Jr., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Chaffin, William Wells, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Chalkley, Dora Green, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Chalkley, Herbert Ellsworth, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Chalkley, Mollie Courtney, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Chalkley, Olive Anderson, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Chalkley, Otway Hebron, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Chalkley, Samuella, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Chalmers, Dwight Moody, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Chalmers, Fortunata Scott, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Chalmers, Horace Hall, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Chalmers, Mary Scott, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Chalmers, Pauline Watts, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Chalmers, William Ferguson, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Chamberlain, Mary Josephine, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Chamberlayne, Ethel Bird, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Chamberlayne, Robert S., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Chamberlayne, Virginia Dilworth, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Chamberlin, Hattie May, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Chambers, Lucille Myra, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Chambers, Merrett Allen, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Chamblee, Ernest E., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Chandler, Bobby Harold, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Chandler, Stella B., 1975 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Chaney, Pauline Rucker, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Chaney, Raymond Lee, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Chaney, Stephie Lee, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Chapin, Cornelius Colton, Jr., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Chapin, Emma Tyler, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Chapin, Marietta P., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Chapman, Annie E., 1924 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Chappell, Frank H., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Chappell, Grace Williams, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Charles, Madalyn W., 1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Charleton, Hylah Curtis, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Cheatham, Clare Davis, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cheatham, Irene Agnes, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Cheatham, Mary Prince, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Cheatham, Roselle Bradley, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Cheatham, Russell Lyle, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Cheatham, Thomas Henry, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Cheek, Douglas Southall Freeman, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Chelf, Annie Deitrick, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Chelf, Annie Greer, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Chelf, Lewis G., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Chelf, R. E., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Chelf, Thomas Wilber, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Chelf, Willie Douglas Gibson Green, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Chenery, Mary Beverley, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Chenery, Richard Leffingwell, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Chernault, Elizabeth Cora, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Chernault, Mary Douglas, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Chesley, Almond Lloyd, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Chesterfield, Elizabeth Crump, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Chesterman, Ellie Frayser, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Chesterman, Evan R., 1980 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Chesterman, Evan Ragland, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Chesterman, Julia Hughes, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Chewning, Carlyle Mason, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Chewning, Clarence Conway, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Chewning, Louise Harper, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Chewning, Virginia Lee Miller, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Chichester, Mary Anne, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Chichester, Peyton Moncure, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Chichester, Randolph Bolling, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Chichester, Richard H. L., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Chilcott, Corrie Hall, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Childers, Elizabeth Gardner, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Childress, Helen N., 1985 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Childress, Sarah H., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Childrey, Laura, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Childrey, Mary Crooks, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Childrey, Roy, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Chilton, Robert Lee, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Chilton, William Chapman, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Chisolm, Helen Garnett, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Chisolm, William E., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Chizever, Danny Allen, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Chouke, Lenore Hicks, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Chrisman, Lucie Carter, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Christian, Andrew D., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Christian, Anna McMullan, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Christian, Annie Jeffries, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Christian, Aya B., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Christian, Bessie Bowe, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Christian, Bessie McDowell, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Christian, Bessie Palmer, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Christian, Catherine Emerson, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Christian, Elizabeth Wilson, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Christian, Emily Huxter, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Christian, Emma, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Christian, Frances Williamson, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Christian, Frank Gordon, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Christian, George L., Jr., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Christian, Helen D., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Christian, Isaac Hill, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Christian, J. Addie, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Christian, John Newton, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Christian, John Newton, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Christian, Joseph Allan, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Christian, Kate Brockenbrough Newton, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Christian, Langdon Taylor, Jr., 1975 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Christian, Laura V., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Christian, Lightfoot Sims, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Christian, Lucy F., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Christian, Martha Harrison, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Christian, Martha Shiflett, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Christian, Mary Agnes, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Christian, Mary Agnes Thornhill, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Christian, Mary Baldwin, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Christian, Mary Elizabeth, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Christian, Mary H., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Christian, Mary Louisa, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Christian, Nathaniel Fleming, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Christian, R. Colston, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Christian, Rebecca Beverley Ruffin, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Christian, Robert Llewellyn, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Christian, Ruth Valentine, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Christian, Stuart G., 1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Christian, Thomas S., 1975 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Christian, William Asbury, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Christian, William Benjamin, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Christian, William D., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Christie, Carney Pitcher, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Christie, Mary V., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Christy, John Charles, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Church, Elizabeth Lewis, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Church, James M., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 0)
- Church, James Scott, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Cidley, Nannie B., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Claiborne, Hazel Otey, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Claiborne, Herbert Augustine, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Claiborne, Virginia Christian, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Claiborne, Walter Blair, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Clark, Ada Brooke, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Clark, Alice Peirce, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Clark, Alva Bernard, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Clark, Ann Louise, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Clark, Annie Day, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Clark, Elizabeth Rob, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Clark, John Niven, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Clark, Josephine Glasgow, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Clark, Louise Jarvis, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Clark, Marcella Jane Lecky, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Clark, Mary E., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Clark, Pearl Brown, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Clark, Shreve, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Clarke, Alice Blair, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Clarke, Christian Harwood, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Clarke, Douglas E., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Clarke, Ella D., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Clarke, Ethel C., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Clarke, Ethel Palmer, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Clarke, Frank V., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Clarke, George Stanley, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Clarke, Heath Christian, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Clarke, Howard Earnest, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Clarke, Irene Dunn, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Clarke, Ruth L., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Clarke, Willette H., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Clary, Alice Roberta, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Clary, Augusta Pearl, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Clason, Elizabeth, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Clatterbuck, Thomas William, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Clay, Ada C., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Clay, Albert H., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Clay, Charles Henry, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Clay, Courtney M., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Clay, Elizabeth Douglas, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Clay, Elizabeth Douglas (2 folders), 1945 (disinterred 1948) (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Clay, Julia Belle, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Claybrook, Harriet Lightfoot, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Clayton, Burkett Sale, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Clayton, Hay Battaile, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Clayton, Mattie Stephens, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Claytor, Patsey Jordan, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Cleaveland, George Julius, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Cleek, George Bratton, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Clement, Benjamin Bullock, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Clement, Eli A., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Clement, Kathryn Lee Powell, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Clement, Lorene Jackson, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Clemons, William Nelson, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Clery, Henry, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Clintsman, Bertha Norman, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Clintsman, Frederick Wooley, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Clopton, Harvey Archer, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Clopton, Harvie Archer, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Clopton, Sarah Eleanor, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Clows, Mary McCormick, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Cluverius, Mary P. F., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Coale, Basil Webster, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Coale, Ida Flippen, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Coalter, Roger Gregory, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Coates, Emily W., 1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Coates, Nancy Shewmake, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Cobb, Edward Thomas, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Cobb, Henry Wellington, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Cobb, Sallie Wills, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Cochran, Carlisle Callahan, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Cochran, Etta Merritt, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Cochran, James Leon, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Cochran, Kathleen R., 1973 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Cochran, Mary William, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Cock, Jerome, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Cocke, Charles Curtis, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Cocke, Edmund Randolph, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Cocke, Elizabeth, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Cocke, Elizabeth Randolph, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Cocke, Harriet T., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Cocke, Thomas Francis, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Cocke, William A., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cocke, William Horner, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Cocker, George B., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Cockey, May Tolson, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Coder, Mary B., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cofer, Anne Gwathmey, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Cofer, Edward Benjamin, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Cofer, Nellie Sweeny, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Coffman, Felicia Livingston, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Cogbill, David, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Coghill, Harvie de Jarnette, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Coke, Anne Elizabeth Harrison, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Coke, John Archer, Jr., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Colbert, Lisa Michelle [infant], 1971 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Cole, Carter Anderson, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Cole, Charles F., 1973 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Cole, Dean Baldwin, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Cole, Edward Martin, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Cole, Frank Walter, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Cole, James Riley, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Cole, June Margaret C., 1975 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Cole, Kathlyn Davis, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Cole, Lewellyn Garland, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Cole, Lucy Davis, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Cole, Rachel, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Coleman, Charles Wallace, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Coleman, Clara Mason, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Coleman, Clarence Dudley, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Coleman, Daisye Chalmers, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Coleman, Edna R., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Coleman, Elizabeth Blanton, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Coleman, Frank Selwyn, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Coleman, James, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Coleman, James Monroe, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Coleman, Lewis Andrew, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Coleman, Norman Virginius, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Coleman, Richard Franklin, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Coleman, Ruth Threadcraft, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Coleman, Virginia French, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Coleman, Virginia Hall, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Coles, Lucy Preston, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Coles, Walter D., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Collier, Frances Burgwyn, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Collier, Grace Harrison, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Collings, Charlotte Cleapor, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Collins, Allen G., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Collins, Arthur B., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Collins, Arthur Bernard, Jr., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Collins, Carl Charles, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Collins, Cora Wood, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Collins, Eugene M., Jr., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Collins, Helen Marrie, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Collins, Margaret Wright,, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Colvig, Janice Carol, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Colvig, John B., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Colvig, Kathryn Baldwin, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Combes, Charles I., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Combs, Emma Love, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Combs, Everett Randolph, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Combs, Morgan L., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Combs, Nancy, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Combs, Rossa C., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Comer, Nannie V., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Compton, Agnes, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Compton, Edyth Christian, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Compton, George Pierce, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Comstock, Bertha Elizabeth, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Comstock, Edward David, n. d. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Comstock, Hattie Eliza Walker, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Comstock, William McDowell, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Conant, Lillie Hening, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Cone, Archie Pleasants, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Cone, Eliza Leake, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Cone, Joseph, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Cone, Leila M., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Conley, James David, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Connell, Anne Mitchell, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Connell, Joseph Paulson, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Connell, Richard Grant, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Conquest, Elise Lowndes, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Conquest, Emma Parker, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Conquest, Pleasonton Laws, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Conquest, Pleasonton Laws, Jr., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Conrad, Margaret Tegram, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Conrad, Parker T., 1974 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Conrad, William A. S., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Conrey, Mary, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Converse, Henry Augustus, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Cook, Estella Milspaugh, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Cook, George Frederick, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Cook, Helen Reid, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Cook, Huestis Pratt, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Cook, John W., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Cook, Lavinia Elizabeth, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Cook, Margaret Scott, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cook, Mary Latimer, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Cook, Mary Virginia, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Cook, Sarah Ashton, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Cooke, Albert Bullock, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Cooke, Dua Ford, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Cooke, Estella Florence, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cooke, James Watkins, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Cooke, John Elliott, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Cooke, Juanita Franklin, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Cooke, Katherine W., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Cooke, Lucy Littlepage, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Cooke, Lucy Waddill, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Cooke, Mary, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Cooke, Mary Elizabeth, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Cooke, Mary Hearn, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Cooke, Opel Ann [infant], 1965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Cooke, Sarah Caswell, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Cooke, William, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cooley, Mary Allen, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Coons, Betty Cannon, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Cooper, Elizabeth Knight, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Cooper, George, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Cooper, Peggy Allen, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Cooper, Sarah Elizabeth, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Copeland, Grace B. Cunningham, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Copeland, Lela, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Copeland, Randolph Scott, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Copeland, Richard W., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Copley, Ernest L., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Copley, William Wilkerson, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Copper, Thomas, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Corbell, Edna Wright, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Corbell, Robert Thurston, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Corbett, Murial Webb, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Corbin, Carrie Massey, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Cordier, Betsey Burwell Page, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Cordier, Helen Wood, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Cordrey, Rosetta, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Corkern, Paul Allen, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Corling, Anna Blanche, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Corling, Emily Adele, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Cormack, Mary W., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Cormack, William Alexander, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Cornwall, Lorena Atlee, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Corprew, Bartee, Edwin, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Corprew, Edwin Elovin, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Corprew, Trenna Olivia, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Correll, Campsie Belcher, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Corson, Leonard B., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Corson, Sallie Taylor, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Cortley, Phyllis, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Cosby, Eliza George Cowherd, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Cosby, Louise Tatum, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Cosner, Stella Kuhn, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Costello, Rosalie M., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Cottrell, Bessie Herbert, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Cottrell, Julia Crump, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Cottrell, R. Stuart, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Coulter, Margaret B., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Coulter, Matthew C., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Council, Carlyle James, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Courtney, Edwin Hill, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Courtney, Irving V., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Courtney, James Alfred, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Courtney, Lou DeVona Kerr, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Courtney, Mollie Catlin, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Courtney, Robert Hull, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Courtney, Sally Browne Fleet, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Couser, Elsie Wood, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Coutts, James, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Cove, Margaret Saunders, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Coverton, Jane G., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Covey, Marie Ryan, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Cowan, Andrew Stiles, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Cowan, Elizabeth Regina B., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Cowan, Mary Elizabeth Hopkins, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Cowan, William Jefferson, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Cowardin, Edward M., 1981 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Cowardin, Lela Bouldin Shewmake, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Cowin, Alice Adamson, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Cowling, Edward William, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Cowling, Mary Elizabeth, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Cowling, Minnie Studds, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Cox, Alice E., 1978 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Cox, Anna Beverley Vaden, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Cox, Anna Wheeler, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Cox, Faye Alta, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Cox, Frederic Hamilton, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Cox, Hallie Hall, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Cox, John Henry, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Cox, Joseph C., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Cox, Joseph Edward, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Cox, Latham Wright, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Coyl, Andrew McNair, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Coyne, Anna Elizabeth, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)